President Adam W. Herbert Speeches, 2003-2008 C344
Indiana University Archives
President Adam W. Herbert speeches
2003-2008
2004-2007
Indiana University Archives
Indiana University. President
C344
3 cubic feet 3 boxes
Adam W. Herbert served as President of Indiana University 2003-2007. Collection consists of speeches given by President Herbert during his tenure at Indiana University as well as a few speeches he delivered as President Emeritus.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research. Advance notice required.
Biographical Note/Administrative History
Adam William Herbert, Jr. was born on December 1, 1943 in Muskogee, Oklahoma. He earned a Bachelor of Arts in Political Science in 1966 and a Master of Public Administration degree in 1968 from the University of Southern California. Herbert received his Doctor of Philosophy degree in urban affairs and public administration from the University of Pittsburgh in 1971. He has served as a professor and in administrative roles at several universities including the University of Southern California, Virginia Tech, University of North Florida, Florida International University, Howard University, and the University of Pittsburgh. Herbert served as the 17th president of Indiana University from 2003-2007 and has the distinction of serving IU as its first African American president. As president of IU, Herbert oversaw several new initiatives in teaching, research, and public engagement. After leaving IU, Herbert and his wife Karen moved to Jacksonville, Florida.
Arrangement
Speeches of President Adam Herbert arranged chronologically.
Scope and Content Note
This collection consists of the speeches given by Adam Herbert during his tenure as Indiana University's 17th president, dating June 2003- December 2007 and during the transition period of January to May 2008.
Some highlights of this collection include all of the commencement addresses given by President Herbert, the eulogy of football Coach Terry Hoeppner, and speeches made at both student and professional events. Some events of note are pep rallies for football and basketball (such as the annual Oaken Bucket game against Purdue); receptions for Wells Scholars and other scholarships recipients; committee meetings (such as budget and diversity committees); alumni meetings and dinners, both national and international; and conferences such as the IU Women's colloquium.
Acquisition Information
Accession 2008/064
Provenance
Transferred from President Herbert's speech writer Susan Moke.
Appraisal
Photocopies of speeches recycled. One box of miscellaneous materials returned to the accession for later processing.
College orations --Indiana University.; College presidents --Indiana --Bloomington --Archives.; College presidents --Indiana --Bloomington --History --21st century --Sources.; Indiana University. President -- Archives; Indiana University -- History -- 21st century -- Sources; Herbert, Adam W. (Adam William), 1943- -- Archives; Herbert, Adam W. (Adam William), 1943- -- Speeches -- Selections
- Speeches, 2003-2008 (Box 1)
  - Summary of comments at Board of Trustees meeting, 5 June 2003 (Box 1)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 14 August 2003 (Box 1)
  - Coaches meeting, 24 August 2003 (Box 1)
  - Athletics Committee Annual Retreat, 24 August 2003 (Box 1)
  - Wells Scholars Reception, 24 August 2003 (Box 1)
  - Freshmen Induction, 27 August 2003 (Box 1)
  - Bloomington Economic Development Corporation, 9 September 2003 (Box 1)
  - Greater Bloomington Chapter of Commerce, 10 September 2003 (Box 1)
  - Diversity reception, 11 September 2003 (Box 1)
  - Indiana's Blueprint for Higher Education, 12 September 2003 (Box 1)
  - IU Northwest Fall Convocation, 15 September 2003 (Box 1)
  - Information Commons Ribbon Cutting, 18 September 2003 (Box 1)
  - Dedication of Research Building II at IU-PU Indianapolis, 30 September 2003 (Box 1)
  - Don Weaver Retirement Reception, 3 October 2003 (Box 1)
  - Marchin Luther King Commission Welcome Reception, 7 October 2003 (Box 1)
  - Neal- Marchall Reception, 11 October 2003 (Box 1)
  - IU Foundation Board of Directors Dinner, 9 October 2003 (Box 1)
  - IU Foundation Board, 10 October 2003 (Box 1)
  - Homecoming Lunch, 11 October 2003 (Box 1)
  - UFC Update, 14 October 2003 (Box 1)
  - State Budget Committee, 16 October 2003 (Box 1)
  - IU Northwest Gala, 6 November 2003 (Box 1)
  - IU Alliance of Distinguished Rank Professors Fall Dinner, 20 October 2003 (Box 1)
  - SPEA Faculty Reception, 4 November 2003 (Box 1)
  - President Circle, 7 November 2003 (Box 1)
  - Economic Club of Indianapolis, 10 November 2003 (Box 1)
  - Annual Meeting Council of the College of Arts and Sciences, 13 November 2003 (Box 1)
  - IU/PU Trustee Toast, 21 November 2003 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Association Staff Meeting, 3 December 2003 (Box 1)
  - Installation Ceremony for Chancellor Charles R. Bantz, 4 December 2003 (Box 1)
  - Executive Session, 4 December 2003 (Box 1)
  - University Club, 9 December 2003 (Box 1)
  - Winter Commencement, 20 December 2003 (Box 1)
  - IUPUI Faculty Council, 13 January 2004 (Box 1)
  - Deans of IUPUI, 14 January 2004 (Box 1)
  - Annual Martin Luther King Jr. Celebration, 19 January 2004 (Box 1)
  - Bloomington Faculty Council, 20 January 2004 (Box 1)
  - Graduate School Task Force, 28 January 2004 (Box 1)
  - IU Board of Trustees, 30 January 2004 (Box 1)
  - IU Alumni Club of Atlanta, 3 February 2004 (Box 1)
  - Sarasota Alumni Club Reception, 6 February 2004 (Box 1)
  - IU Foundation Board of Directors, 7 February 2004 (Box 1)
  - Coach Jerry Yeagley's Retirement Dinner, 14 February 2004 (Box 1)
  - Arts Leadership Forum Luncheon, 18 February 2004 (Box 1)
  - IU Southeast Chancellor's Medallion Dinner, 18 February 2004 (Box 1)
  - Trustee Tuition Forum, 23 March 2004 (Box 1)
  - Bloomington Economic Development Luncheon, 23 March 2004 (Box 1)
  - IU Southeast Alumni, 1 April 2004 (Box 1)
  - President Herbert's Inaugural Address, 15 April 2004 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Colloquium on Excellence in Teaching, 27 April 2004 (Box 1)
  - Trustees of Indiana University, 7 May 2004 (Box 1)
  - IU Bloomington Commencement Address, 8 May 2004 (Box 1)
  - IU-PU Fort Wayne Commencement, 12 May 2004 (Box 1)
  - IU Northwest Commencement, 13 May 2004 (Box 1)
  - IU East Commencement, 14 May 2004 (Box 1)
  - IUPUI Campus Apartments Dedication Ceremony, 26 May 2004 (Box 1)
  - Innovator of the Year Award, 26 May 2004 (Box 1)
  - Science Building Groundbreaking, 3 June 2004 (Box 1)
  - Rotary Club of Evansville, Indiana, 8 June 2004 (Box 1)
  - IU Boards of Trustees, 11 June 2004 (Box 1)
  - IU Foundation Board Dinner, 17 June 2004 (Box 1)
  - IU Alumni Association Executive Council, 19 June 2004 (Box 1)
  - IU Board of Trustees, 12 August 2004 (Box 1)
  - Wells Scholars Welcome Reception, 22 August 2004 (Box 1)
  - Freshman Induction, 25 August 2004 (Box 1)
  - Opening Remarks for the IUPUI Campaign Press Conference, 26 August 2004 (Box 1)
  - Symposium on Black Philanthropy, 26 August 2004 (Box 1)
  - Budget Presentation for the Higher Education Council, 1 September 2004 (Box 1)
  - Groundbreaking Ceremony for Medical Sciences Building, 1 September 2004 (Box 1)
  - New Athletics Director Announcement, 2 September 2004 (Box 1)
  - Alliance of Distinguished and Named Professors, 23 September 2004 (Box 1)
  - TechPoint Summit VII Panel, 29 September 2004 (Box 1)
  - Greater Educational Opportunities Foundation, 30 September 2004 (Box 1)
  - Indiana Rotary Club, 5 October 2004 (Box 1)
  - Art Sinsabaugh Reception and Dinner, 6 October 2004 (Box 1)
  - United States Foreign Relations Committee, 6 October 2004 (Box 1)
  - Retirement Party for IU President Assistant Cindy Smith, 7 October 2004 (Box 1)
  - NCAA Kansas City speech, 8 October 2004 (Box 1)
  - Informatics/Communications Technology Complex (ICTC) dedication, IUPUI, 7 October 2004; (folder 1 of 2) (Box 1)
  - Informatics/Communications Technology Complex (ICTC) dedication, IUPUI, 7 October 2004; (folder 2 of 2) (Box 1)
  - State Budget, 14 October 2004 (Box 1)
  - New President's Circle Members, 15 October 2004 (Box 1)
  - NASPAA, 21 October 2004 (Box 1)
  - Elkhart County NAACP Annual Dinner, 21 October 2004 (Box 1)
  - IUPUI Comprehensive Campaign, 23 October 2004 (Box 1)
  - IU Foundation Board Dinner, 28 October 2004 (Box 1)
  - Homecoming Brunch, 29 October 2004 (Box 1)
  - IU Foundation Board of Directors, 29 October 2004 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Associations, 4 November 2004 (Box 1)
  - IU Board of Trustees, 5 November 2004 (Box 1)
  - IU Women's Colloquium, 5 November 2004 (Box 1)
  - IUPUI School of Law Board of Visitors and Alumni Reception, 12 November 2004 (Box 1)
  - Regional Chancellors' Advisory Board Retreat, 12 November 2004 (Box 1)
  - IU/Purdue Trustees Oaken Bucket Dinner, 19 November 2004 (Box 1)
  - Old Oaken Bucket Brunch, 20 November 2004 (Box 1)
  - Dinner for Trustee Jeff Cohen, 30 November 2004 (Box 1)
  - IU Board of Trustees, 3 December 2004 (Box 1)
  - New Football Coach Announcement (Terry Hoeppner), 15 December 2004 (Box 1)
  - METACyt Press Conference, 16 December 2004 (Box 1)
  - New Football Coach Announcement (Terry Hoeppner), 17 December 2004 (Box 1)
  - IUB Winter Commencement, 18 December 2004 (Box 1)
  - House Ways and Means Committee Indiana General Assembly, 11 January 2005 (Box 1)
  - Annual Martin Luther King Jr. Celebration, 11 January 2005 (Box 1)
  - Opening Reception for the Human Genome Exhibit at the Indiana State Museum, 20 January 2005 (Box 1)
  - IU Board of Trustees, 28 January 2005 (Box 1)
  - LA/Orange County Alumni Club, 30 January 2005 (Box 1)
  - Dallas/Ft. Worth Alumni Club, 31 January 2005 (Box 1)
  - IU Foundation Board Dinner, 3 February 2005 (Box 1)
  - Phoenix Alumni Club Reception, 4 February 2005 (Box 1)
  - IU Foundation Board Meeting Report, 5 February 2005 (Box 1)
  - IU Faculty Council, 8 February 2005 (Box 1)
  - Hoosiers for Higher Education Annual Statehouse Visit, 8 February 2005 (Box 1)
  - United Way Vanguard Reception, 23 February 2005 (Box 1)
  - IU Board of Trustees, 4 March 2005 (Box 1)
  - IU Founders Day, 6 March 2005 (Box 1)
  - Senate Appropriations Committee of the Indiana General Assembly, 7 March 2005 (Box 1)
  - University Faculty Council, 8 March 2005 (Box 1)
  - Kelly School of Business Annual Conference, 9 March 2005 (Box 1)
  - Campaign for Community Announcement IU East, 25 March 2005 (Box 1)
  - Board of Advisors Meeting for IU East and Purdue University School of Technology, 25 March 2005 (Box 1)
  - South Bend Area Alumni Clubs Reception, 31 March 2005 (Box 1)
  - Lumina Foundation Presidents' Fund Conference, 5 April 2005 (Box 1)
  - University Faculty Council, 12 April 2005 (Box 1)
  - Public Forum on Tuition, 13 April 2005 (Box 1)
  - Introduction of Tuition Presentations, 13 April 2005 (Box 1)
  - 27th Distinguished Black Alumni Awards Ceremony, 23 April 2005 (Box 1)
  - Retirement Festivities for Trevor Brown, 29 April 2005 (Box 1)
  - Honorary Degree Dinner, 6 May 2005 (Box 1)
  - IUB Commencement, 7 May 2005 (Box 1)
  - IUPUI Commencement, 8 May 2005 (Box 1)
  - IU Southeast Commencement, 9 May 2005 (Box 1)
  - IU Kokomo Commencement, 10 May 2005 (Box 1)
  - IU South Bend Commencement, 10 May 2005 (Box 1)
  - IPFW Commencement, 10 May 2005 (Box 1)
  - IU Northwest Commencement, 10 May 2005 (Box 1)
  - IU East Commencement, 12 May 2005 (Box 1)
  - Dedication of Eskenazi Hall, 3 June 2005 (Box 1)
  - IUPUC Bold Aspiration Kick-off, 14 June 2005 (Box 1)
  - IU Foundation Directors, 16 June 2005 (Box 1)
  - IU Foundation Board of Directors, 17 June 2005 (Box 1)
  - Herman B Wells Library Naming, 17 June 2005 (Box 1)
  - Cream and Crimson Barbeque, 18 June 2005 (Box 1)
  - IU Alumni Association Ten Years of Service, 18 June 2005 (Box 1)
  - E. Ross Bartley Awards Reception, 22 June 2005 (Box 2)
  - IU Board of Trustees, 24 June 2005 (Box 2)
  - Dedication of IU Southeast Library, 28 June 2005 (Box 2)
  - WFIU Radio Commentary, August 2005 (Box 2)
  - IU Board of Trustees Recognition Dinner, 15 August 2005 (Box 2)
  - New Trustees Welcome Dinner, 18 August 2005 (Box 2)
  - IU Board of Trustees, 19 August 2005 (Box 2)
  - Bloomington Rotary Club, 23 August 2005 (Box 2)
  - IU Bloomington Freshmen Induction, 24 August 2005 (Box 2)
  - IU Kokomo 60th Anniversary, 25 August 2005 (Box 2)
  - Athlete Welcome Picnic, 28 August 2005 (Box 2)
  - Football Kickoff, 29 August 2005 (Box 2)
  - IU Athletics Staff, 30 August 2005 (Box 2)
  - President's Update, September 2005 (Box 2)
  - Monroe County Cares, 5 September 2005 (Box 2)
  - BioCrossroads/IU Foundation Forum, 7 September 2005 (Box 2)
  - Hoosier Presidential Scholars, 9 September 2005 (Box 2)
  - President's Circle Members, 9 September 2005 (Box 2)
  - Reception at Ruth Johnson's, 14 September 2005 (Box 2)
  - Business Meeting of IU Trustees, 22 September 2005 (Box 2)
  - Clarian Cancer Center Groundbreaking, 22 September 2005 (Box 2)
  - IU Supplier Diversity Day, 22 September 2005 (Box 2)
  - Annual Alliance of Distinguished and Ranked Professors Dinner, 27 September 2005 (Box 2)
  - State of the University Address, 27 September 2005 (Box 2)
  - IUPUI Campus Center Groundbreaking, 30 September 2005 (Box 2)
  - 125th Celebration of the Bayh-Dole Act, 5 October 2005 (Box 2)
  - FACET's DVD remarks, 5 October 2005 (Box 2)
  - IU Foundation Board of Directors, 6 October 2005 (Box 2)
  - Radio Commentary, 7 October 2005 (Box 2)
  - IU vs. University of Illinois Pep Rally, 7 October 2005 (Box 2)
  - IU Foundation Board of Directors, 7 October 2005 (Box 2)
  - Neal Marchall Alumni Club Reception, 8 October 2005 (Box 2)
  - Indiana Association of Collegiate Registrars and Admissions Officers, 19 October 2005 (Box 2)
  - Indiana Logistics Summit Luncheon, 19 October 2005 (Box 2)
  - Naming Ceremony for William J. Godfrey Education Center, 21 October 2005 (Box 2)
  - WFIU Commentary, 24 October 2005 (Box 2)
  - Dedication of Raclin-Carmichael Hall, 25 October 2005 (Box 2)
  - State Budget Committee, 28 October 2005 (Box 2)
  - WFIU Commentary, 1 November 2005 (Box 2)
  - Groundbreaking of Research Building III, 2 November 2005 (Box 2)
  - IU East Alumni Reception, 3 November 2005 (Box 2)
  - IU Board of Trustees, 4 November 2005 (Box 2)
  - Update on Federal Relations, 15 November 2005 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of the renaming of IU School of Music, 17 November 2005 (Box 2)
  - IU/Purdue Board of Trustees Oaken Bucket Dinner, 19 November 2005 (Box 2)
  - IU Faculty Council, 29 November 2005 (Box 2)
  - Cox Scholars Press Conference, 1 December 2005 (Box 2)
  - WFIU Radio Commentary, 2 December 2005 (Box 2)
  - Hoosier Presidential Scholars Medallion Ceremony, 3 December 2005 (Box 2)
  - IU Board of Trustees, 9 December 2005 (Box 2)
  - Honorary Degree Dinner, 16 December 2005 (Box 2)
  - Winter Commencement Address, 17 December 2005 (Box 2)
  - U.S. University President's Summit, 6 January 2006 (Box 2)
  - Annuitants Association of IU, 11 January 2006 (Box 2)
  - Kiwanis, 13 January 2006 (Box 2)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 14 January 2006 (Box 2)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Commemorative Celebration, 16 January 2006 (Box 2)
  - 13th Annual Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Youth Breakfast, 16 January 2006 (Box 2)
  - BioCrossroads Legislators Luncheon, 17 January 2006 (Box 2)
  - Future Fund Entrepreneurial Forum, 17 January 2006 (Box 2)
  - Indianapolis Downtown Kiwanis, 20 January 2006 (Box 2)
  - Greater Cincinnati Chapter of the IU Alumni Association, 25 January 2006 (Box 2)
  - IU Board of Trustees, 3 February 2006 (Box 2)
  - IU Board of Directors Dinner, 9 February 2006 (Box 2)
  - IU Foundation/IU Alumni Association Joint Reception, 10 February 2006 (Box 2)
  - IU Foundation Board, 10 February 2006 (Box 2)
  - 18th Annual Claude Rich Open Scholarship Dinner, 13 February 2006 (Box 2)
  - Assembly Hall Press Conference, 16 February 2006 (Box 2)
  - Vanguard Reception, 16 February 2006 (Box 2)
  - Hoosiers for Higher Education Reception, 21 February 2006 (Box 2)
  - Africana Fest, 23 February 2006 (Box 2)
  - Jacobs School of Music Naming Ceremony, 24 February 2006 (Box 2)
  - Academic Advisor's Council, 24 February 2006 (Box 2)
  - Our Town Premiere Dinner, 24 February 2006 (Box 2)
  - University Faculty Council, 28 February 2006 (Box 2)
  - Monroe County Chapter of IU Alumni Association, 2 March 2006 (Box 2)
  - IU Board of Trustees, 3 March 2006 (Box 2)
  - DC Alumni Chapter Reception, 6 March 2006 (Box 2)
  - Indiana Delegation and Alumni Reception, 7 March 2006 (Box 2)
  - Fairbanks Press Conference, 21 March 2006 (Box 2)
  - Langston University keynote, 23 March 2006 (Box 2)
  - Lee Hamilton Papers Reception, 27 March 2006 (Box 2)
  - New Basketball Coach Announcement, 29 March 2006 (Box 2)
  - U.S. Basketball Writers Association Breakfast, 31 March 2006 (Box 2)
  - Richmond Kiwanis, 31 March 2006 (Box 2)
  - Founders Day, 2 April 2006 (Box 2)
  - Evansville Rotary, 4 April 2006 (Box 2)
  - Wrubel Computing Center, 4 April 2006 (Box 2)
  - Board of Trustees Public Forum, 5 April 2006 (Box 2)
  - IU Southeast Chapter of the Alumni Association, 6 April 2006 (Box 2)
  - IU Kokomo Alumni, 6 April 2006 (Box 2)
  - Honors Day, 9 April 2006 (Box 2)
  - 17th Annual Human Rights Awareness Luncheon, 13 April 2006 (Box 2)
  - HPER Dean's Associate Advisory Board, 20 April 2006 (Box 2)
  - Press Conference Concerning the Deaths of IU Students, 21 April 2006 (Box 2)
  - Commission on Higher Education, 21 April 2006 (Box 2)
  - Bloomington Black Business and Professionals Association, 21 April 2006 (Box 2)
  - IU Board of Trustees, 5 May 2006 (Box 2)
  - IU Bloomington Commencement Address, 6 May 2006 (Box 2)
  - IU Southeast Commencement Address, 8 May 2006 (Box 2)
  - IU Kokomo Commencement Address, 9 May 2006 (Box 2)
  - IU South Bend Commencement Address, 9 May 2006 (Box 2)
  - IU/PU Fort Wayne Commencement Address, 10 May 2006 (Box 2)
  - IU Northwest Commencement Address, 11 May 2006 (Box 2)
  - IU East Commencement Address, 12 May 2006 (Box 2)
  - IUPUI Commencement Address, 14 May 2006 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Awards Day Luncheon, 20 May 2006 (Box 2)
  - Richmond InNovembertion Center Luncheon, 31 May 2006 (Box 2)
  - IU Kokomo Alumni Association, 8 June 2006 (Box 2)
  - IU Board of Trustees, 8 June 2006 (Box 2)
  - Senior Staff Meeting (Commemorating J. Terry Clapacs), 12 June 2006 (Box 2)
  - Staff Long Service and Retirement Ceremony, 12 June 2006 (Box 2)
  - Radio Spot, 13 June 2006 (Box 2)
  - WFIU Commentary, 13 June 2006 (Box 2)
  - IU Foundation Board Dinner, 15 June 2006 (Box 2)
  - Distinguished Alumni Reception, 16 June 2006 (Box 2)
  - Annual Cream and Crimson Barbeque, 17 June 2006 (Box 2)
  - IU Alumni Association Executive Council, 17 June 2006 (Box 2)
  - Mini-University Opening, 19 June 2006 (Box 2)
  - Equal Opportunity Day Luncheon, 20 June 2006 (Box 2)
  - Dunes Medical/Professional Building Dedication, 22 June 2006 (Box 2)
  - Indiana State Fair, 10 August 2006 (Box 3)
  - Major Donors Reception, 11 August 2006 (Box 3)
  - Wells Scholars Reception, 12 August 2006 (Box 3)
  - Super Computer Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 22 August 2006 (Box 3)
  - Presidential Scholars Reception, 23 August 2006 (Box 3)
  - Freshmen Induction, 26 August 2006 (Box 3)
  - 12th Annual Kokomo Chapter of the Indiana Black Expo, 31 August 2006 (Box 3)
  - Reception for Advisory Board Members and Alumni Leaders, 31 August 2006 (Box 3)
  - Indiana Commission for Higher Education Breakfast Briefing, 8 September 2006 (Box 3)
  - Indiana Commission for Higher Education, 8 September 2006 (Box 3)
  - Ball State/Big Red Warm-up, 9 September 2006 (Box 3)
  - Alliance of Distinguished and Named Professors, 25 September 2006 (Box 3)
  - President's Circle Member, 29 September 2006 (Box 3)
  - State Appropriation Request, 17 October 2006 (Box 3)
  - IU Foundation Board Dinner, 25 October 2006 (Box 3)
  - IU Foundation Dinner in honor of John Ryan, 26 October 2006 (Box 3)
  - Homecoming Luncheon, 28 October 2006 (Box 3)
  - Bloomington Faculty Council, 31 October 2006 (Box 3)
  - Business Meeting of the Trustees, 2 November 2006 (Box 3)
  - Women's Colloquium, 3 November 2006 (Box 3)
  - American Chamber of Commerce of Japan, 13 November 2006 (Box 3)
  - IU LeaD Seminar, 13 November 2006 (Box 3)
  - Center on Philanthropy Press Conference, 21 November2006 (Box 3)
  - IU Alumni Association Awards, 8 December 2006 (Box 3)
  - Business Meeting of IU Trustees, 8 December 2006 (Box 3)
  - LeaD Seminar, 13 December 2006 (Box 3)
  - State Budget Hearing, 13 December 2006 (Box 3)
  - Transforming Indiana Press Conference, 14 December 2006 (Box 3)
  - IU Bloomington Winter Commencement Address, 16 December 2006 (Box 3)
  - Indiana Higher Education Commission, 12 January 2007 (Box 3)
  - Martin University Honorary Doctorate Program, 14 January 2007 (Box 3)
  - IU Faculty Council, 23 January 2007 (Box 3)
  - State Appropriations Request, 25 January 2007 (Box 3)
  - Retirement Reception for Ken Beckley, 31 January 2007 (Box 3)
  - Business Meeting for IU Trustees, 2 February 2007 (Box 3)
  - IU Foundation Board Dinner, 8 February 2007 (Box 3)
  - IU Foundation Board Report, 10 February 2007 (Box 3)
  - Hoosiers for Higher Education, 20 February 2007 (Box 3)
  - Eli Lilly and Company Black History Month Celebration, 21 February 2007 (Box 3)
  - Hoosier Presidential Scholars Dinner, 23 February 2007 (Box 3)
  - IU Faculty Council, 27 February 2007 (Box 3)
  - 61st Annual Kelley School of Business Conference, 28 February 2007 (Box 3)
  - Trustees of IU Alumni Reception, 1 March 2007 (Box 3)
  - [no subject], 3 March 2007 (Box 3)
  - United Way Vanguard Reception, 6 March 2007 (Box 3)
  - Health Information and Translational Sciences Building, 7 March 2007 (Box 3)
  - Senate Appropriation Hearing, 13 March 2007 (Box 3)
  - Kappa Alpha Psi North Central Province Public Meeting, 23 March 2007 (Box 3)
  - Founders Day Ceremony, 25 March 2007 (Box 3)
  - Washington, D.C. Alumni Indiana Day Reception, 26 March 2007 (Box 3)
  - Washington, D.C. Donors Breakfast, 28 March 2007 (Box 3)
  - STEM Initiative Press Conference, 29 March 2007 (Box 3)
  - Trustees of IU Alumni Reception, 5 April 2007 (Box 3)
  - IU Trustees Business Meeting, 6 April 2007 (Box 3)
  - STEM Partnership Dinner, 10 April 2007 (Box 3)
  - Birch Bayh Papers Reception, 11 April 2007 (Box 3)
  - Announcement of Glick Eye Institute, 13April 2007 (Box 3)
  - National Policy Forum on Minority Entrepreneurship Education, 14 April 2007 (Box 3)
  - IU Faculty Council, 24 April 2007 (Box 3)
  - David Fulton Retirement Dinner, 27 April 2007 (Box 3)
  - FACET Retreat, 27 April 2007 (Box 3)
  - Presidential Portrait Unveiling, 2 May 2007 (Box 3)
  - IU Trustees Business Meeting, 4 May 2007 (Box 3)
  - Honorary Degree Dinner, 5 May 2007 (Box 3)
  - IU Bloomington Commencement Address, 5 May 2007 (Box 3)
  - IU Kokomo Commencement Address, 8 May 2007 (Box 3)
  - IU South Bend Commencement Address, 8 May 2007 (Box 3)
  - IU/PU Fort Wayne Commencement Address, 9 May 2007 (Box 3)
  - IU Northwest Commencement Address, 10 May 2007 (Box 3)
  - IU East Commencement Address, 11 May 2007 (Box 3)
  - IUPUI Commencement Address, 13 May 2007 (Box 3)
  - Board of Trustees Tuition Forum, 21 May 2007 (Box 3)
  - Jack and Linda Gill Symposium, 23 May 2007 (Box 3)
  - IU South Bend Student Housing Groundbreaking, 12 June 2007 (Box 3)
  - IU Foundation Board Dinner, 13 June 2007 (Box 3)
  - IU Alumni Association, 16 June 2007 (Box 3)
  - IU Bloomington Athletic Facilities Groundbreaking Ceremony, 19 June 2007 (Box 3)
  - Trustees of IU Alumni Reception, 21 June 2007 (Box 3)
  - Eulogy for Coach Terry Hoeppner, 23 June 2007 (Box 3)
  - IU Southeast Student Housing Dedication, 27 June 2007 (Box 3)
  - Bloomington Presidential Scholars, 22 August 2007 (Box 3)
  - 35th University Luncheon, University of Florida, 2 October 2007 (Box 3)